{\clip(190,219,190,219)\t(0,600,\clip(100,217,280,220))\t(16600,17100,\clip(190,217,190,220))}m 0 0 m 180 1 l 0 1 l 0 0 l 180 0
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
粲呀粲\h\h\hJennysueyolo\h\h\h\hPhagee
moonie\h\h\h生生生生\h\h\h\hsukichin
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}校对\h&\h后期
夏棒棒\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}总监
大红
片头推广合作洽谈\h请联系普罗米修斯邮箱\hPLMXS2016@GmaiL.com
地窟藏恶
这是在发什么呆
Look at this dick wrinkle.
中午打算带我去哪吃饭
Where are you taking me to lunch?
我要去一趟市中心
I have to head over to midtown.
他们找到什么了吗
They find something?
没有
No.
就是见个面
Just a meeting.
老一套
Same shit.
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
那就明天晚上
Tomorrow night, though,
别他妈又放我鸽子
don't go fucking bailing on me this time.
对你有好处
It'll be good for you.
谁知道呢  也许你会喜欢这小妞
Who knows, you might even like this chick.
八成不会了
Nah, probably not.
但她挺火辣的
She's kind of hot, though, you know?
在口活的时候睁眼睛的那种火辣
Hot in that kind of, keep her eyes open during a BJ
你懂我意思吗
kind of way, feel me?
-我得走了  -行
- I better get going. - All right.
给你
Here.
克劳德
这是什么  连着六个了吗
What is that, six in a row?
八个
Eight.
随你怎么说  混蛋
Yeah, well, whatever, dick,
我下个月再来找你
I'm coming for you next month
你欠我一顿午饭
and you owe me lunch.
今天剩下的时间我都不在了
Oh, um... I'm going to be unavailable for the rest of the day.
-好  没问题  -行
- Sure, no problem. - Okay.
一切还好吗  你没事吧
Is everything good? Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
终于找到了他的母亲
Finally tracked down the mother.
莫莉·柯比
Molly Kirby.
没多大用
Wasn't any help.
她说几个月没见过他了
Said she hadn't seen him in months,
就算见了可能也不会告诉我们
not sure she'd tell us if she had.
那有没有室友
What about a roommate?
女朋友呢
Girlfriend?
我是说  总有人在哪见过他吧
I mean, somebody has to have seen him at some point, right?
问题是
The problem is,
他们卡在最后一步太久了
when they've been this close to the bottom for so long,
要找到他就更难了
it makes it easier to stay under the radar.
你想帮忙  我们很感谢
While we appreciate you wanting to help,
但让我们来处理是最好的
it's best you let us handle it.
尽最大努力往前看
Do what you can to move on.
我理解的  好吗
Hey, I know, okay?
我理解
I know.
但你要听我一句劝
But you got to take it from me,
它会由内而外吞噬你
this shit will eat you up inside.
任其发展  你会什么都不剩
Consume you all together if you let it.
还以为没人会吃这个呢
Didn't think people actually ate these.
显而易见
Apparently.
我们现在设了有机食品区  在
You know, we have an organic section now, it's--
你真的不该吃这个
you really shouldn't eat these.
老实说  我都不会拿这玩意喂狗
Honestly, I wouldn't even feed them to a dog.
不是说不喜欢狗  但你知道的
Not that I don't like dogs, but like, you know.
我们走
太好了
That's nice.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you!
见到你总是很高兴  克劳德
Yes, it's always good to see you, Claude.
-你跳萨尔萨舞吗  -大家好我是凯拉
- Do you salsa? - Hi everyone, I'm Kyra!
-嗨  -欢迎
- Hi. - Welcome.
-还有一个人吗  -是的
- Waiting on one more? - Yes.
-你一定就是莱莉了  -对
- You must be Rylee. - Yes!
他是锋利的利  我是茉莉的莉
Oh, Riley with an I, Y two E's.
-巧了  -可不是吗
- Oops. - I know, right?
这是克劳德
This is Claude.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
太对不起了  我来晚了
So sorry I'm late you guys.
有个混蛋尿在自己身上了
One of the little bastards pissed himself,
我都没法抓狂了
so I can't freaking even,
你怎么样
how are you?
-嗨  -我很好
- Hi! - I'm good.
你们两个
Huh, both of you.
-你好啊帅哥  -见到你真高兴
- Hi, delicious. - So good to see you!
见到你也很开心
Good to see you, too!
索里亚  这是克劳德
Soria, this is Claude.
克劳德  这是索里亚
Claude, this is Soria.
克劳德
Claude.
莱莉什么都告诉我了
Rylee has told me everything,
这简直太  糟糕了
and it's just so... awful.
太可怕了
It's terrible.
别有压力  我们来跳支舞
So, no pressure, let's just do a little dance,
玩得开心一点  今晚舞动起来
have a little fun, get down tonight!
-好吗  -好  那就开始吧
- Yeah? - Okay, let's get started.
不对  我觉得该往后退
No, go back I think.
有进步
Okay, better.
试着去感受音乐
Maybe just try and feel the music,
别太担心步伐
don't worry so much about the steps.
或是节奏
Or rhythm.
还不错
Not bad.
但也没有很好
Not great, either.
好了  我们来做点旋转动作
Okay, okay, maybe let's just do a little spin.
-我吗  -对
- Yeah? - Yeah.
先往外一步
So we're going to step out
然后转到搭档的臂弯里
and spin into our partner's arms. Okay?
很好
Nice.
就这么简单  准备好了吗
Just that easy, ready?
-准备好了  -好
- Yes. - Okay.
错了  抱歉
Oh, oopsie, oh, sorry.
五  六  七  八
And five, six, seven, eight.
-靠  -你  这
- Fuck! - Oh, you, ah, yeah, that's…
糟了  糟了  你还好吗
oh, shit, shit, are you all right?
还好  还好  我没事  没事
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine, fine, fine, fine.
-你还好吗  -还好  靠
- Are you all right? - Ah, yeah, s-- shit.
我觉得我  她数得有点快
Yeah, I think I just, uh, she went a little fast
-我数错拍子了  -把她扶起来
- and I missed my count. - Yeah, get her up.
-我们把你扶起来  -不要  你俩别
- We'll get you up. - No, you guys, stop.
起来  起来  好了
Up, up, up, up, there we go.
好的  继续走
Okay, keep going.
-我的天  -问题不大
- Oh, God. - It's okay.
给你找个地方坐下来
Let's get you to sit down.
-好  -看上去挺糟的
- Okay, ah! - That looks bad.
-你真强壮  -那是当然
- You're so strong. - Oh, yeah.
我们扶着坐到这里吧
We're going to put you right here.
就是这样
There we go.
就这  慢慢坐下
Get it, oh, there we go.
我没事  我真的没事
I'm fine. I'm fine you guys.
我能帮什么忙吗  给你拿点冰块之类的
I-- Can I help? Can I get you some ice or something?
不用了
Oh, no, no.
谢谢
Thanks.
好吧
Okay.
-老天  -能给我点布洛芬吗
- Oh, jeez. - Um, maybe, maybe just some Ibuprofen or--
当然  没问题
Yeah, no problem.
我去拿点
I'll grab something.
要是能载我回家就太好了
Or just a ride home would be nice.
她和你顺路  你载她吧
She's on your way, you should take her.
当然了  没问题
Sure, yeah, no problem.
改日再来吗
Rain check?
好
Yeah.
你们两个呢  想继续吗
How about you two, you want to finish up?
既然我们都在这了
Uh, well, we're here.
你觉得呢  莱  莱
What do you say, Ry Ry, huh?
好耶
Olé!
-给你  -好的  我们开始吧
- Here you go. - All right, here we go.
来吧  开始
Let's go, come on.
通常来说那的确是个问题  是吧
Ah, well that's usually the problem though, isn't it?
但我看人很准的
But I am a pretty good judge of character.
我可以通过外观来判断他们
I can tell a person's appearance just by looking at them.
-很厉害  -那是
- That's impressive. - Yeah.
但我看不出他们结婚没有
What I can't seem to tell is whether they're married or not.
我的上两段  可能是三段恋情
The last two, oh, maybe three relationships?
都是已婚人士  你能信吗
All married guys. Can you believe that?
怎么说  也许是因为他们压抑的原始欲望
I don't know, maybe it's just they're pent-up primal desires
我才会被吸引
that I'm attracted to?
又或者是我有一种吸引已婚人士的特质
Or maybe I just have this scent that attracts married guys?
我也不清楚
I don't know.
这到你家了吗
Is this it?
是的
Oh, yeah.
你着急走吗
Are you in a hurry?
-来  抱歉  -站稳了  没事
- Okay. Yep, sorry. - Oh, got it. Okay.
-来  -在
- Yeah. - Yeah, it's uh...
在最上面
it's just all the way... at the top.
我想也是
Yeah, figured.
好了
Okay.
-很好  -很好
- Okay, ooh! - Yeah, okay.
靠
Oh, shit.
你可以  我们可以加把劲
Maybe if you just, we just power through
快点上去
real fast then, huh, yeah?
算了  好吧  我们慢慢走
Or not, okay, we'll go slow.
你还好吗
Oh, okay, are you all right?
我把你扶到
Okay, I'll put you--
-这里就行了  -那里  好的
- Okay, right here is good. - Right there, okay.
好了
Okay.
好了  好了
Yeah, yeah, okay.
到了
Okay, so.
-谢谢你  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
你上床了吗
Did you bang it out?
黄片呢
Porn?
没有  不是
No, and, uh, no.
-别再给我牵线了  -真的吗
- And, uh, no more setups. - Really?
老天  我发誓她闻起来就很饥渴
God, I swear she just smelled horny.
算了  管他的
Oh, well, whatever.
聊聊那个指导老师怎么样
Can we talk about that instructor, though?
那是怎么一回事
What is that all about?
你知道的
Ah yeah, you know.
莱莉说
Rylee was all like,
"你能别用那玩意戳我吗
"Would you please stop poking me with that thing?
你有病啊"
What is your problem?"
我说  "抱歉  亲爱的
And I was all like, "Sorry, sweetheart,
你跳起舞来太性感了"
you're just such a sexy dancer!"
她没吃我这套
She didn't buy it.
她知道就是莫名的勃起
She knew it was strange boner.
你要去哪
Hey, where are you going?
我有个午餐会议
Uh, I've got a lunch meeting.
-什么  -是的
- What? - Yeah.
好吧
Oh, all right.
可别介意
Don't mind if I do.
看看
Yeah.
保证不把你秘密说出去
Your secret's safe with me.
没关系的
It's all right.
多谢
Thanks.
♪ 来这的是诱饵 ♪
♪ Ah it's the bait come here ♪
凯拉舞房
-对不起  -住嘴
- I'm sorry… - Stop.
听我说  兄弟  你必须要听我说
No, listen. Listen, man, you got to let me tell you, okay?
-我只想告诉你  -住嘴
- I'm just trying to tell you what… - Stop.
-我  你必须听我说我当时  -住嘴
- I'm, I… You gotta let me tell you what I was… - Stop.
-我不是  我不是  -够了
- I didn't, I didn't… - Enough!
我不是  我不是故意的  我
I didn't, I didn't mean to do it, okay, I, s--
你必须听我说
Look, you got to just let me tell you
发生了什么  你必须
what happened! Okay, you got--
你想拿我怎么办
What are you going to do with me, huh?
你要永远把我关在这里吗
You going to keep me down here forever?
你他妈怎么就不能放下
What don't you just fucking get it over with?
真的没有  但你也知道
There, there really isn't, but something you know.
-但  但  我是说  -约翰
- But, but, but, I mean… - John?
约翰
John!
约翰  我有听说  约翰
John, this is, this is what I'm hearing, John.
我听说你不信任我  约翰
I'm hearing that you don't trust me, John.
-我是这么听说的  -不不不  不是的
- That's what I'm hearing. - No, no, no, that's not.
-不是的  -不  你听我说
No? -No, I'm telling you.
不对  不是的  打住
No, no, stop.
-但我要试着  -停下来  听着
- But it just, I'm going to try-- - Stop, listen.
约翰  我想让你这么做
John, this, this is what I want you to do.
我要你给镇上所有的商店打电话   约翰
I want you to call every shop in town, John.
我要你他妈的做充足的笔记  约翰
I want you to take copious fucking notes, John.
然后  试试能不能做成神奇的生意
And, and, find that magic, hocus pocus fucking deal, okay?
当你意识到这根本就不存在时
And when you realize that it doesn't exist,
我的报价才是合法的
and that what I'm offering is legit,
我希望你那会给我电话
then I want you to call me back
然后我就可以跟你说滚开  约翰
so I can tell you to fuck off, John.
-是吗  -你知道吗  是的
- Oh, is that so? - You know, you know what? Yeah--
我挺忙的  我们俩都省省力气吧
since I'm a busy guy, I'm going to save us both the effort.
滚开  约翰
Fuck off, John.
知道吗  你是对的  你完全正确
You know what? You're right, you're right.
提议很公平  我相信你
The offer's fair, I trust you.
你一直对我直言不讳
You've been a straight shooter with me and I,
-我告诉她我们和你一起去  -很好
- I'll tell her we're going with you. - Good.
把你的东西发过来吧
Then send in your shit.
你应该约她出去
You should ask her out.
谁
Who?
什么  那个指导老师吗
What, the instructor?
是的  凯拉
Yeah, Kyra.
凯拉  凯拉
Kyra, Kyra.
哦  凯拉  噢  噢  凯拉
Uh, oh, Kyra, oh, oh, Kyra!
光说她名字我嘴巴都能高潮  伙计
Just saying her name gives me a fucking mouthgasm, dude.
前几天晚上我很生莱的气
I was so mad at Ry the other night,
我们做爱的时候  我开始想她
I started thinking about her while we were having sex.
感觉还不错
Oh, it was nice.
超级快  进来出去  射在她肚子上
Super quick, though. Um, just in, out... right on her stomach.
-你怎么  怎么能  -怎么了
- Ugh, how do you, how do you-- - What,
老兄  这玩意是双向的
oh, dude, that shit goes both ways.
相信我  这就是为什么会有用
Trust me, that's why it works.
我向你保证  就她而言
I promise you, as far as she's concerned,
我是他妈的查宁·塔图姆给她新生
I was Channing fucking Tatum digging her out,
《魔力麦克》主演
越来越深入  给她来个原版《魔力麦克》
going deep, giving her the old Magic Mike.
2012年喜剧电影  关于脱衣舞男的故事
我不在乎
I don't care.
你知道吗  你  就像某种
You know, you, you are like some kind of
有诗意但下流的学者  你知道吗
poetic yet filthy savant, you know that?
我喜欢这说法
Whoa, I like that.
来吧  约她出来
Come on, ask her out.
-不可能  -伙计  我知道有点奇怪
- Not happening. - Ugh, come on dude, I know it's weird
还有一些不成文的规定
and there's some unwritten rule,
但我得说  跟你在一起有一半的时间
but I, I got to say man, half the time I don't know
我不知道该说什么  该做什么
what to say or how to act around you.
事实上  我确定的是  大部分的时候
In fact, what I do know is that I am of zero help
我都无法帮助你  宽慰你  一直都是
or comfort to you most of the time, all the time!
伙计  你他妈过得很苦
Ugh, dude, you are fucking miserable.
她不会愿意你这样的
And she wouldn't want it like that.
你好
Hi... Hi.
-你好  -你好
-Hi. - Hi.
克劳德对吗  莱利夫妇的朋友
Claude, right? Friend of the Rileys?
是的  是我
Yeah, that's me, yeah.
那么  有什么需要我帮忙的吗
So, can I help you?
是的  有的  我
Yes, yeah, um, yeah, I, I was, um,
我在想  或许能回到这里来
I was thinking about, um, getting back in to it, maybe?
你明白吗  就  上几节课
You know, uh, just, just, uh, just a couple of lessons.
上课  你想上萨尔萨舞的课吗
Lessons, you want salsa lessons?
是的  我一直对这个挺感兴趣的
Yeah or, um, you know I-- I've always been interested in the,
狐步舞
um, the foxtrot.
狐步舞吗
Foxtrot?
-真可惜  -是吗
- Uh, that's a shame. - It is?
是啊  我是说你那天开车路过
Yeah, I mean after you pussed out the other day
赶紧低头  开车过去的事
and did that whole duck and cover drive away thing?
我想也许这次你会  鼓起勇气约我出去
I thought maybe this time you'd, uh, sacked up to ask me out.
什么
What?
不  我没有  什么  我  我没有
No, I didn't, what are, I, I, I didn't.
-我有  -你有
- I did. - You did.
我有  是的  我
I did, yeah, I, that--
你愿意  你愿意和我一起共进晚餐吗
um, would you, would you like to have dinner with me?
在  在不久的将来
Sometime, um, in the, in the near future?
好  我愿意
Yeah, I would.
在不久的将来
Sometime in the near future.
好的
Okay.
-怎么了  -莫莉·柯比是吗
- Well? - Molly Kirby?
是我
You got her.
不知道能不能跟你谈谈
I wonder if I could talk to you
你的儿子  洛根
about your son, Logan?
听着  我已经告诉过你们了
Look, I done told you,
混蛋  我没有见过他
motherfuckers, I haven't seen him.
我和那些混蛋不是一起的
I'm not with the motherfuckers.
你真是个有趣的混蛋
You're a real funny asshole, huh?
我只想和你谈谈
I just want to talk.
我敢肯定你他妈的一点都不惊讶
I'm sure you're not fucking shocked to find out
我不是那种典型的母亲  对吗
that I wasn't the most nurturing of mothers, hm?
严厉的爱  知道吗  这对孩子有好处
Tough love, you know? It's good for kids.
那他父亲呢  还在吗
What about the, uh, his dad? Is he still around?
你他妈的在跟我开玩笑  是吗
You're fucking kidding, right?
这是什么狗屁脱口秀吗
Is this some sort of talk show shit?
你说得对
You're right.
让他们排一排  随便指一个  就是了
Just line them up and point and, uh, there you go.
打电话给莫里  恭喜  你是父亲了
Call Maury. Congratulations, you are the father.
那他小时候呢
What about as a kid?
是什么样子的
What was he like?
他小时候是什么样子的
What was he like as a kid?
我他妈的不知道  就是个孩子
I don't fucking know. He was a fucking kid!
你在写什么  传记什么的吗
What are you writing, uh, a biographical or something?
是那种有钱人的内疚  是吗
Hm? You, you got some rich guy guilt?
-不  我没  没在写什么  -那什么
- No, I'm not, um, I'm not, uh, writing-- - Well then what the,
那你他妈的是在干什么
what the fuck?
你想怎样
What are you after?
我
I--
我不知道
I don't know.
怎么  你是孤单吗
What, are you lonely?
如果是这样  或许我能帮上忙
Because that's maybe something I can help with.
不是
No.
不用  谢谢
No, thank you.
他说  "不用  谢谢"
He says, "No, thank you."
你真是个有趣的混蛋
You are a funny asshole.
你还没有告诉我  你为什么要找他
You still haven't told me why you're looking for him.
洛根  他
Logan, he, um...
他
He--
我在浪费时间
I'm wasting my time.
等等  你叫什么名字
Hey, oh, what's your name?
我叫克劳德
It's Claude.
嘿  伙计
Hey, buddy.
把约翰的包裹拿回来了
Got John's package back.
是单大生意
It's a big one.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
很好  谢谢
Great, thank you.
只是  再检查一下签名
Just, uh, double check the signatures and...
放到我桌子上
...um, leave it on my desk.
好的
All right. Okay.
Yep.
他在这  棒呆了  是不是
Ah, there he is! Yeah, yeah, what, what!
我得走了  稍后给你打电话
I got to run, I'll call you later.
伙计  我要你帮个忙
Oh, oh, oh, bro, I need a solid!
老婆让我们今晚去那种红酒油画的地方
Wife's got us going to this wine and paint bullshit tonight,
我要人当托儿  你听说过那种地方吗
I need a wing man. You ever heard of that garbage?
不行  今晚不行
I can't, not tonight.
兄弟  有红酒和油画
Brother, it's wine and painting!
要是我长出个阴道呢  拜托
What if I grow a vagina? Please,
-求你了  求你了  -我有
- please, please, please, please. - I have a...
-拜托  -我有点事
- Please. - ...I have a thing.
-有点事  -是的
- A, a thing? - Yeah.
是真有事的有事吗
Like a, like a thing thing?
对  真有事
Yeah, a thing thing.
那是和谁呢
Oh, with who who?
凯拉
Kyra.
对不起  我很抱歉
I'm sorry. Oh, I'm so sorry.
严格来说  这是  这是融合餐厅
It technically, um, technically this is, uh, this is fusion.
-是吗  -是的  我读到过说
- Uh-huh. - Yeah. I, uh, I read that, um,
这种融合餐厅最适合初次约会
that-- that fusion is... good for first dates.
适合初次约会  你读到过
Good for first dates, you, you read that?
在网上  是的
Online, yeah.
这  这太傻了  太蠢了
It's, it's really stupid. It's so dumb.
那么  你朋友
So, um, your friends.
-莱利夫妇吗  -是的
- The Rileys? - Mm-hm.
他们很奇怪
They're weird.
他们真的  真的太奇怪了
They really, really are.
我有种感觉
I got the feeling
我成了某种手淫仪式的对象
that I was the subject of some masturbatorial ritual.
-是这个词吗  - 我想是的
- Is that a word? - I, I think so, yeah.
我想是的  或者就应该  是你
I think so, or it should be and, uh, you were.
天哪  这是奉承吗
Oh, God, it's flattering, right?
我不知道  我  你知道  他
I don't know, I, you know, he,
他能对着那些东西手淫
he masturbates to those, um,
那些汉堡包的广告
to those hamburger commercials,
我的天哪
Oh, my God. -so--
好吧
Okay.
你知道  我的前任喜欢那样
You know, my ex was like that.
我以前每隔一天就能抓他一次
I used to catch him, like, every other day.
真的吗
Really?
真的  我们以前纸巾一打一打地买
Really. We used to go through paper towels by the dozen.
总是在镜子前面
Always in front of a mirror.
-是恋物癖  -是恋  纸巾吗
- Fetish thing. - Fetish, um, the, the paper towels?
不是  是镜子
No... the mirrors.
试衣间里的噩梦
A nightmare in fitting rooms.
好吧
Yikes.
是反射什么什么症
It was cato-something-philia.
一年内结婚又离婚
Married and divorced within a year.
那你呢  结过婚吗
How about you, ever married?
有过
Yeah.
好的  然后呢
Okay and?
你都已经知道我前任的破事了
You know all about my pud whacking ex.
说出来吧
Out with it.
怎么  是离婚吗
What, divorced?
撕逼撕得很厉害吗
Did it get ugly?
是女同性恋吗
Oh, lesbian?
拜托  告诉我是因为她疯了
Come on, please tell me she went taco!
是吗  所以  她是很肌肉猛女
Yes? So, what did she go butchy
还是像色情片里一样好看
or like TV porn pretty?
她去世了
She passed away.
妈的  该死
Oh, shit. Ah, shit.
我不  我不知道该说什么了
I don't, I don't know what-- I don't what to say, um--
告诉我你是开玩笑的  你
Tell me you're joking, you--
你在耍我吗
You're fucking with me?
我的天
Oh, my God.
多长时间了
Um, how long?
八个月了
Eight months.
八个月  这
Eight? This, uh--
时间够长了吗
Is, is that enough time?
这个  我不知道
Well, I, I don't know. Um.
我不知道是否有
I don't know if there's uh, like a,
一个期限或是  确定的时限
you know a set, like a set or, or definitive.
不  不  不  好吧  我很抱歉
No, no, no, no, okay, I'm sorry.
对不起  我真的很不擅长这个
I'm sorry, I, I'm just really bad at this.
我  我
And I, and I, um...
我们可以  可以走了吗
Could we, could we just get out of here?
好的  好的  没问题
Okay, yeah, yeah, no problem.
不  不  不  我还想再一起待会
No, no, no, no, I, I still want to hang.
我是说如果你愿意的话
I mean if you do.
只是  我搞砸了
It's just, I, I fucked this up,
还有这融合餐厅的味道
and, and the smell of this fusion.
-还有女同性恋的事  -说真的  听着
- And, and the lesbian thing, and-- - Yeah, honestly, look,
你不可能提前预料到的
um, there's, there's no way you could have known.
好吧
Okay.
抱歉  你  你还有什么别的计划吗
Um, I'm sorry, you, you had something else planned?
是的  我
Yeah, I, yeah.
还是离开这里吧
Get out of here though.
小时候  我吃东西糊了一嘴时  我爸爸
As a kid, when I'd get all messy, my dad
总会把纸巾舔湿了
would always like lick a napkin
来擦我的脸
and wipe my face with it.
是的  我记得这种事  还有
Oh, yeah, I remember that. And the, uh,
他自己口水的味道
this smell of his own spit.
恶心
And, ugh.
这一定是
It must be like a...
怪怪的  作为父亲的本能  对吧
A weird, instinctual dad thing, yeah?
-是的  -对
- Hm. - Yeah.
对  就是这样
Yup, that's it!
非常感谢你帮我缓解了那种恶心
Thank you very much for helping me relive that trauma.
这个约会的糟糕食物和冰激凌
This date, bad food, ice cream,
让我觉得我只有15岁
I feel like I'm 15 and you're going to try
你随时都想尝试和我来一发
and fill me up at any minute.
不  我认为来点怀旧会很有趣
Nah, I, I, I thought, um, a bit of nostalgia would be fun.
那么  接下来干嘛  上车
Mm-hm. So, what's next, putt putt and making out
在去恐龙王国的路上亲热吗
on the Kingdom of the Dinosaurs ride?
第二次约会
Ah, second date.
通常到那会我才会想要摸胸
Hm, that's usually when I go for boob, too.
所以你今晚很安全
So, you're safe tonight.
好啊
Hm.
你知道吗  以前我常常需要花好几个小时
Wow, that you know, it used to take me like hours
才能鼓起这种勇气
to work up to that kind of courage.
我觉得好廉价
I feel so cheap.
-对不起  -不
- I'm sorry. - No.
给你摸
Here you go.
来啊
Go on.
公平起见  就很快地摸一下
Just a quick feelsy, only fair.
好了
Yeah?
就这样
That's it?
感觉怎么样
How was it?
-还不错  -不错
- It's good. - Good?
很棒  感觉特别好
Great, it was, um, awesome.
极品胸部  非常令人愉悦  对
Awesome boob, very, very enjoyable, yeah.
我的如何
How was mine?
像被蜜蜂蛰了一下
Small little bee sting.
手感很好的大乳头
like a handful, big nipples.
谢谢你送我回来
Well, uh, thank you for the throw back.
不客气
You're welcome, yeah.
你还好吗
You all right?
嗯  不客气
Yeah, you're welcome.
-你已经说过了  -对
- You said that. - Yeah.
如果是因为进展太快  我可以理解
Look, I get if it's too soon.
不不  没有
No, no, no, no, um, it's not.
其实  我想要再试一次
Um, in fact, I'd like another try.
下次来点好吃的
Hm, something edible, next time?
我会考虑的
I'll think about it.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿  你还好吗
Man, you okay?
嘿  对不起  对不起  对不起
Yo, hey, I'm sorry, look, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
你好
Hi.
嘿  我今晚去约会了
Hey. I had a date tonight.
我还挺乐在其中的
And, and I en-- enjoyed it.
对此我感觉很糟
And I feel awful.
好吧
Yeah.
我去看了你母亲
Um, I, uh, I visited your mother.
我母亲
My, my mother?
你去看了她  什么意思
You, you visited her, what, what's that mean?
她
She's...
她挺有趣
...she's interesting.
有趣
Interesting?
你会打电话给她吗
You going to call her?
-我应该吗  -当然了
- Should I? - For sure, yeah.
是不是有什么规则
Isn't there, isn't there some kind of rule?
不不  那些规矩太老派了
Nah, nah, man, nah. See that's, that's some old school shit.
你应该打给她
You should call her.
嘿  我妈怎么样
Hey, how's, how's my mom?
不错
Good.
挺担心你
Worried about you.
好吧
Yeah.
嘿  伙计  你介意
Hey, hey, dude, do you mind
给我看会电视吗
the TV maybe?
给
Here.
我拿这个  我拿这个能干嘛
And what am I, what am I supposed to do with this?
对  对  我活该
Yes, yes, I, I deserve that.
当然  好的  我会去的
Sure, yeah, yeah, I'm up for that.
好
Okay.
好  我会顺路过去的
Yeah, I, no, I'll swing by, mm-hm.
好的  很简单
Okay, easy enough.
好的  没问题  回见  好
Okay, all right, I'll see you then. Okay.
好的
All right.
嗨
Hey!
看看这谁  都不吃狗粮了  还记得我吗
Look who's off the dog food... Remember?
嗯
Yeah.
我想是的
I guess so, yeah.
多亏了你
Thanks to you.
真的吗
Aw, really?
太好了
Awesome.
至少有了进步
At least there's progress.
你给她打电话了
You called her?
她打的
She did.
所以你以前跳过舞吗
So you've dance before?
一点点  你懂的  我有点生疏了
Uh, a little. Yeah, I'm a little rusty, you know.
我也这么想的
Yeah, I thought so.
动作做得挺好
Yeah. Decent moves.
你总是可以从一个人的走路姿势
And you can always tell by someone's walk
判断出他懂不懂节奏
if they have rhythm.
所以你学过什么舞  社交舞
So what was it, ballroom?
或许是踢踏舞
Tap, maybe?
一点点
A little.
主要是街舞
Hip hop mostly.
操
Fuck off.
真实生活中是嘻哈男孩
Real life B-Boy.
闭嘴  你骗人
Shut up, you're such a liar.
没有  一点点机械舞和锁舞
No, no. A little popping, locking.
好啊  我挑战你
Okay, challenge.
我接受挑战
Challenge accepted.
这是C步吗
Is that a C Walk?
对
Yeah.
你懂的  帮派舞
Yeah, you know, gangsta.
C步和帮派舞都是不同的街舞类型
你懂的  道上混的
You know, just, uh, hustling the streets.
想挣点钱
Trying to earn that dollar.
这  是为了赢得
Uh, it was, um, yeah, it was, uh, just for girls,
姑娘们的欢心而已
and to impress girls.
是吗
Is that right?
-那么奏效了吗  -一点点
- Is it working? - A little bit.
是吗
Yeah?
太好了  因为通常
Good, you know, because usually,
其实在做完这些动作之后
actually after I, um, after I do something like that
我就问"嘿美女  你想来段磨舞吗"
I'm like, "yo girl, you want to freak this?"
一种舞伴贴身摩擦的舞蹈
磨舞
Freak?
我完全不记得磨舞怎么跳了
I completely forgot about freaking.
啊对哦
Oh, yeah, hm.
等一下
Hold that thought.
让我来看看你有什么本事
See what you got.
对  多吃点
Mm, yeah, get in there.
跳磨舞会让你这么饿吗
Does freaking always make you this hungry?
对  这就是为什么我高中的时候那么胖
Yeah, it's why I was so fat in high school.
体型庞大
Huge.
我很庆幸以前没有那种强制演出
I'm just glad they didn't have that intervention show back then.
因为我家里人就会说
You know, because my family would have been like,
"克劳德  我们爱你
"Claude, we love you,
但我们很担心你的磨舞
but we're worried about your freaking.
有点失去掌控了"
It's really gotten out of hand."
我也一样  不过手掌换成肛门
Same here, but mine would have been for anal.
我妈妈的保护欲特别强
My mom was pretty protective.
不  我只是开玩笑
No, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding.
她不在乎  喜欢这些和屁股有关的东西
She didn't care. Loved the butt stuff.
是的
No.
再次表示抱歉
Well, again, sorry about that.
没事
That's all right.
现在知道为什么我选择去餐厅和电影院了
Now we know why I choose restaurants and the movies.
成交
Deal.
进来吗  你个怪胎
Coming in, you weirdo?
我没布恩农场的酒了
I'm all out of Boone's Farm.
普通的红酒可以吗
Regular wine okay?
可以  完美
Ha, perfect, yeah.
所以你拥有工作室多久了
So, how long have you had the studio for?
我这个工作室已经两年了  克劳德
I have had the studio for two years, Claude.
有没有什么是你一直想要的
And is it, um, something, you, you, always wanted?
有  我从小就一直想有一个
Yeah. Yeah, I always wanted to own a shitty
小小的舞蹈工作室
little dance studio since I was a little girl.
人生目标达成了
Life goal, complete.
所以一切都进展得很顺利  你
So, it's going well? Um, you
别说了
Just stop.
有很多  你可以
That's plenty. You can just.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我的天  你是不是
Oh, my God, are you, are you?
我做不到
I can't.
我的天
Oh, my.
书怎么样
How's the book?
还不错  我渐渐读进去了
It's not bad now that I'm getting' used to it.
我见到她时  她就在读这本书
It's a book that she was reading when I saw her.
我第一次见到她时  她读的就是这本
The book, um, the first time I saw her, she was reading it.
就这本书
That, that book.
知道吗  这是我这辈子读的第一本书
Well, you know, this, this is the first book that I ever read.
是我这辈子第一次看书
As in like, the first time I ever read any book.
你懂的  不是儿童读物之类的书
You know, that wasn't like a kiddie book or something.
我觉得我出轨了
It felt like I was, uh, cheating on her.
她坐在那里
She was there, and...
她坐在我腿上
...she's on my lap,
我脑子里只有她
and all I can think about was her.
好吧
Yeah.
你知道吗  我第一次上床
You know the, um, the first girl I ever got with
是和一个叫玛莎的红发小妞
was this red-haired chick named Martha.
通常  这不是我的菜  但你知道
And normally I-- I am not into shit like that, but you know,
玛莎她简直是没话说
but Martha she was like, like, damn.
然后我就  惊呆了
And I was like, whoa.
皮肤那么光滑细腻
Skin all creamy and shit.
我不知道我在干什么
And I-- I didn't know what I was doing,
但是玛莎知道
but you know, Martha she knew some things.
她懂的
Yeah, she knew some things.
但自那以后  感觉就没那么好了
But like ever since her it's all been downhill.
似乎没有人足够好到能满足我
It was like nobody is good enough.
你懂吗  没人可以让我有那奇妙的感觉
You know, nobody has that magic touch.
所以后来我就开始让别的女孩
So, finally I just, I started asking girls
做玛莎会做的事情
to do things like Martha would do.
你知道的  我不会直接说
You know, I, I wouldn't say like,
"嘿  像玛莎一样做"
"Hey, do it like Martha's doing it."
但是我会耐心引导她们
But I would like kind of instruct them.
但是  玛莎一直都在
But, you know, Martha was always there,
当我和别人搞的时候一直在我的脑海中
in my head when I was with the others.
就这样
So.
我觉得你要有麻烦了
Yo, I think you got problems.
啥
What?
那个探长来找你了
The detective guy is here to see you, ha ha!
所以  你喜欢当侦探吗
So, do you like being a detective?
麦吉探长
Detective McGee?
-有那么久了  -对  有几年了
- Been that long? - A few years, yeah.
所以你是找到什么线索了吗
Hey, so did you find something or...?
我接到了莫莉·柯比的电话
Got a call from Molly Kirby.
是的  她说你去看她了
Right. She, um, said you stopped by.
她觉得你是我们警方的人
Got the impression you were from our office.
她是  我没这么跟她说过
She got, I didn't tell her that.
你为什么会去她那
Why were you there?
-我不知道  -你不知道
- I don't know. - You don't know?
我不知道
I don't.
听着  我很迷茫
Look I get, uh, confused.
很焦虑  还很
anxious, and, and, and--
沮丧  你们就不会
frustrated that you know, you guys haven't.
她说你威胁她了
She said you threatened her.
什么  没有
What, no.
没有  绝对没有
No, absolutely not!
那是怎么回事
What's that about?
什么怎么回事
What's what?
我的车库里有个拳击袋
I got a bag in the garage.
只是发泄一下
Just letting off a little steam.
好吧
Right.
好吧  你应该带副手套
Well, uh, you should get some gloves.
你就那么走了  连句话都没留
You just left, nothing, not a word?
我  我  我
Mm, no, I, I, I, um.
我  我可能嘀咕了两句
I, I might have mumbled something,
然后  然后  就好像
and, and, and then it's all kind of a--
但她亮出胸器了  对吗
But like her stuff was out, right?
我
I...
我可能哭了
...might have been crying.
她的皮肤柔软吗
But her skin was soft?
身体像舞者那样紧实吗
Her body tight, like dancer tight?
抱歉  我胡说的  很抱歉
Hm, I'm sorry, that's totally fucked up. I'm sorry.
这太糟了  太糟了
That's terrible, it's terrible.
-你哭了  我是说  -好了  我懂的
- The crying, I mean... - Yes, yeah, I know.
-谢谢  -太糟了
- Thank you. - It's terrible.
也许  你想来点面条吗
You want some noodles, maybe?
会让你感觉好些
Make it better.
♪ 面条带给你欢乐 ♪
♪ Noodles make you happy ♪
你好啊
Oh, hey.
你好
Hey. Hi.
那天晚上的事  我很抱歉
Hey, I'm, I'm so sorry about the other night.
不  你完全用不着道歉
No, you, you, you don't have to, um, apologize at all.
应该是我感到抱歉
I'm sorry.
你
Um, you're, uh,
你真的很棒
you're wonderful.
然后我  我  我
And I'm, um, I'm yeah, I'm, I'm, I'm,
我现在一团糟
I'm pretty fucked up right now and,
我  我甚至不知道
I like, I, I don't even--
我懂
I get it.
其实我真的很喜欢你
I really like you, though.
我喜欢  我是说  我真的喜欢你
I like, I mean, I really like you.
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
是的  但是我  你知道的
Yeah, but I, you know,
我理解的  你懂的
I'd understand, you know,
如果在那之后
if af-- after that.
你是说你哭的事吗
The crying?
所以  我真的哭了
So I was actually crying?
是的
Yup.
-我的天啊  -还挺可爱的
- Oh, God. - It was kind of cute.
-真的吗  -并不是
- Really? - No.
但  也许有一天会是个好故事
But, you know, maybe it'll make a good story someday?
是啊  值得一次一次地回味
Yeah, something to relive over and over and over again.
所以说
So...
你还想再试一次吗
...do you want another round?
要是我保证不试着跟你上床的话
That is if I promise not to try and have sex with you?
我觉得这样挺好  我愿意
I think that's agreeable, yeah.
那就这么说定了
Then it's a deal.
说定了
Deal.
我读完了
I finished the book.
从头至尾
Cover to cover.
感觉不错
It feels kind of good.
我知道你的意思  就是
Yeah, I think I know what you mean. Like,
翻页的时候  看过的越来越多
you know, when the, when pages get thinner on one side
剩余的越来越少
and fatter on the other.
对  就是那样
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
我是说  大部分我都没太理解
I mean, I don't understand most of the shit,
但是里面有些女性很有意思
but like... there's some funny ass females yo.
她们也  也会搞砸
And them be like, like, they fucked up, too,
但从某种程度上讲
but like in a way
就好像在说  我懂你  知道吗
that makes you say like I get you. You know?
那个操蛋的南希  对吧
And that fucking Nancy, right?
等等  我不记得有什么南希
Wait, I don't, I don't remember a Nancy.
南希
Nancy.
-作者吗  -是啊  就是她
- The author? - Yeah, her.
兄弟  她像是  啪  啪  啪
Oh, my god, dude, she's just like bam, bam, bam, bam, bam,
丢下一颗又一颗的宝石
just like dropping one gem after another.
她有点刻薄  但是
And she's kind of mean, but like,
很时髦  也很性感
like sassy, too, so it's sexy.
他们本应都是自命不凡的家伙
And they supposed to be all hoity toity and shit,
但是他们喜欢做爱
but they like fucked.
一直不停地做
They fucked. All the way.
透漏出什么是人性  是吧
Kind of tells you about people, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
她挺野的  兄弟
She's wild, man.
天啊
Wow!
你没开玩笑吧
You weren't kidding.
{\frz3\f莱-10\shad0\bord0\blur1\4c&H020080&\4a&H00&\b1\2c&H020080&\2a&H00&\be0\c&H804007&\1a&H00&\fnSimHei\fs18\pos(251.8,124.5)}斯塔芬高尔夫
{\frz3\f莱-10\shad0\bord0\blur1\4c&H020080&\4a&H00&\b1\c&H5F4586&\1a&H00&\2c&H020080&\2a&H00&\be0\fn.SF NS Text\fs18\pos(245.9,145.6)}家庭娱乐中心
我得提醒你  我很擅长这个的
I have to warn you, I am very, very good at this.
-真的吗  -是啊
- Yeah, sure. - Mm-hm.
你拿的什么
What is that?
这是
This is, um...
我的推杆
...my putter.
你带了自己的推杆来
You bring your own putter?
这比租的好
It's better than the rentals.
不  没门  放回去
No, no way, put it back.
为什么啊
What, why?
谁会到迷你高尔夫场带自己的推杆
Who brings their own putter to miniature golf?
别这样  太丢人了
No, no it's embarrassing!
不会  拜托  这并不丢人啊
No, come on, it's not embarrassing.
我宁愿坐在那些青少年对面
I would rather sit in front of those teenagers
让你趴在我怀里哭
with you weeping on my breasts again,
也不愿被人看到和一个自带推杆的男人
before being seen with a man who brings his very own
一起迷你高尔夫
grown-up putter to miniature golf.
-打得好  -谢谢
- Oh, well done! - Thank you.
不  不能这样
Uh, uh, uh, no, no.
为什么
What?
你得打完  还没到自由推杆
You follow that through, there are no gimmes.
好吧PGA  我们照这规矩打吗
All right, PGA, is that how we're doing this?
PGA是美国职业高尔夫球运动员协会
你说过你很擅长  不是吗
You did say you were good, right?
♪ 当我们耳边响起了疯狂 ♪
♪ When the madness Rings our ears ♪
♪ 我只想占有你 ♪
♪ I just want to have you ♪
还挺不错的
It's pretty good, though.
♪ 告诉我你也想要 ♪
♪ Tell me that you want to ♪
♪ 让你的火花变成金色 ♪
♪ With your spark That turns to gold ♪
♪  你的眼睛 ♪
♪ And your eyes that ♪
♪ 展露你的灵魂 ♪
♪ Bare your soul ♪
♪ 这真的重要吗 ♪
♪ Does it really matter ♪
♪ 告诉我你想要什么 ♪
♪ Tell me what you're after ♪
♪ 现在就关灯  宝贝 ♪
♪ Lights out, baby now ♪
洞在这边
The hole is this way.
♪ 你是我的  别落后了 ♪
♪ You're mine, Don't fall behind ♪
♪ 我想要感受你的全部 ♪
♪ I love to feel you all over ♪
中不了
Miss!
打不中
Miss it!
♪ 不管你做什么 ♪
♪ Don't care what you do ♪
♪ 我会点燃你的心火 ♪
♪ I'll light the fire Inside of you ♪
击球
Hit the ball!
♪ 我们一触即发 ♪
♪ And we can make an explosion ♪
如果这个球你中了  我就
If you get this, I will...
♪ 即使你走得太远 ♪
♪ Even when You've gone too far ♪
♪ 我都会守住你的心 ♪
♪ Will always have my heart ♪
♪ 靠近你 ♪
♪ I will hold you closer ♪
-多谢  -不用客气
- Thank you! - You're welcome.
怎么了
What?
你真是
You are, um--
你数学真不怎么样
you are really bad at math.
咱俩平局
We tied.
-是的  -什么
- Yeah. - Oh, what?
再来决胜局  混蛋
Tiebreaker, biatch!
好吧  决胜局
All right, tiebreaker.
♪ 不管你做什么 ♪
♪ Don't care what you do ♪
♪ 我会点燃你的心火 ♪
♪ I'll light the fire Inside of you ♪
♪ 我们一触即发 ♪
♪ And we can make an explosion ♪
♪ 现在就关灯  宝贝 ♪
♪ Lights out, baby now ♪
-棒  -你不是吧
- Yes! - Oh, you didn't.
-干得漂亮  -走吧
- Beauty! - Get out of here.
♪ 不管你做什么 ♪
♪ Don't care what you do ♪
♪ 我会点燃你的心火 ♪
♪ I'll light the fire Inside of you ♪
♪ 我们一触即发 ♪
♪ And we can make an explosion ♪
快看他的小乳头
Oh, look at those tiny nipples!
快住嘴
Oh, stop!
玩得真开心  抱歉你输了
Awesome time. Sorry you lost.
是啊  我知道你是真心道歉
Oh, yeah, I'm sure you are, yeah.
如果我用了自带的推杆
You know, if I, if I'd only had my putter--
你真是个没朋友的小可怜
You'd be a sad, sad lonely man with no friends.
我不知道啊  我想
I don't know. I think, um, think
我内心住着个小孩
that little kid, I think he was
他眨眼了
into me. He winked, I think.
-不是吧  -是的
- No. - Mm-hm, yeah.
我漏了这茬
I missed that.
谢谢
Thank you.
莱利明晚要办生日派对
So, uh, Riley's having a birthday party tomorrow night
严格来说  如果带你去的话
and, technically, I don't have to get him a present
我就不用准备礼物了
if you were to show up with me.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
先是拉我和高尔夫小哥的皮条
First pimping me out to the golf kid
现在又来这个
and now this.
我真的很希望你来
And I'd really like it if you came with me
这样就又能和你一起玩一晚上了
and I got to spend another night hanging out with you.
那好呀
Okay then.
见鬼  我肯定也很喜欢你
Damn it. I must really, really like you, too.
因为我做了关于他的噩梦
Because I've had actual nightmares about him
梦见了他可能对自己做的事
and the things he might do to himself.
那先谢谢你
Then thank you.
撤了
Peace out.
我一直很忙
I've been busy.
这是我最喜爱的其中一本
It's one of my favorites.
好厚
It's thick.
-是啊  -很好
- Yeah. - Nice.
跟你说  我认真的  兄弟
I'm telling you, I mean seriously dude,
如果我老婆
if my wife--
-嘘  -怎么了
- Shh... - What, oh.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
凯拉告诉我和塔蒂安娜
Kyra tells Tattianna and I
说你舞跳得好
that you are quite the dancer.
她夸张了
She's exaggerating.
-不  我才没有  -不  她就是
- No, I'm not. - Yeah, she is.
你有自己的动作
You have moves.
-这家伙可会磨舞了  -磨舞啊
- Downright freak this one. - Oh, freaky!
好吧  再来一轮  好吗
Okay, drinks, drinks, refill?
莫斯科骡鸡尾酒  大都会鸡尾酒
Mule, Cosmo,
大都会  灰雁伏特加和汤力水  对吗
Cosmo, Goose and tonic, yeah?
-莱利  你来帮我吧  -干什么
- Riley, why don't you come join me? - What?
我只有两只手  但我们需要拿四杯
I've got two hands and we need four drinks, so.
好的
Okay.
快来
Come on.
说真的  你俩超般配的
Seriously, you guys are like a perfect match.
不是啦  我们就是放松放松
Oh, no, we're just chilling. You know, with his stuff.
天啊  我知道  他是最棒的
Oh, my god, I know. And he's like the best.
简直就是史上最完美的人
Like, literally the best guy ever. Like, literally...
还有他妻子
and his wife...
也是个超级大好人
...so super-duper great, too.
-你认识她吗  -是的
- Oh, you, you knew her? - Mm-hm.
我们还真没聊过这事
Yeah, we, we haven't really talked about it.
我觉得这对他来说承受的太多了
I think it's too much for him.
我只希望他们能找到那个混蛋
Well, I just hope they find that fucker.
抱歉  你说什么  找谁
I'm sorry, what? Uh, who?
就是那个家伙
The guy, you know?
他们还没捉到他
They haven't caught him yet.
一想到他还在四处游荡
To think he's still out there.
克劳德就像个天使
Claude is like an angel,
要是我  就会带把枪
because I would be out there
遇上了就真准备用
with a gun like, seriously.
女士们
Ladies.
谢谢
Thank you.
我好像溅到身上了
I think I spilled on myself.
至少现在  我们都会做噩梦
At least now, you know, we'll both be having nightmares.
说实话  我从未看到他们牵手
Honestly, I've never even seen them like hold hands,
更别说他们做的其他什么事了
let alone doing whatever they were doing.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You okay? - For sure.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我只是
Yeah, I just, uh,
塔蒂安娜跟我说到了你妻子
Tattianna was telling me about your wife.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
其实你可以直接问我
Well, you could have just asked me.
我没问  她就说了  我没有问她
No, I didn't, she just started going, I didn't ask her.
好吧
Right.
我想让你知道现在有我在
I wanted you to know that I want to be here.
不管多长时间
However long it takes you,
我想这样
I want this.
是吗
Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
好
Okay.
我们能
Can we just, um,
我们能再谈谈莱利吗  就一小会
can we just talk about Riley for like, one more second?
拜托了
Please?
抱歉  我现在不愿意想他的
I'm sorry, I didn't want to think about him just now.
我真的不想  但他之前做的那些动作
I really didn't, but it's just what he pulled back there,
真是见鬼了
it's just come on.
-快点  喝了  -谢谢你
- Come on, drink up.  - Ah, God bless you.
-你会好点的  -昨天很尴尬吗
- You'll feel much better.  - Was it embarrassing?
嗨
Hi.
-早上好  -成了
- Good morning.  -Ah, yes it is.
你要去哪  先生
Where do you think you're going, Mr?
-停下  -我想知道所有细节
- Stop.  - I want to know everything.
我觉得你得讲个故事
I think you've got a story to tell.
-停  停  -嘿  怎么了  怎么了
- Stop, stop! - Hey, what, what, what, what?
所以呢
So?
所以
So.
所以我们在一起度过了一晚上
So we, we, we hung out all night, and--
我们看了很多电视节目还点了披萨
We binged watched some TV shows and we ordered pizza.
然后呢
And?
-没有  -没有吗
- No. - No?
我们
We're…
我们还在等
We're waiting.
你们还在等
You're waiting?
-你们还在等  -是的
- You're waiting? - Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
你知道  这真的
You know, actually, um,
还真的  有点甜
actually, I think that's kind of sweet.
你真这么想的
You do?
是的
Yeah, I do.
怎么了  真的
What, I do!
我其实  我也很喜欢搞浪漫的
I mean, I, I like romance and shit, too.
你知道吗
You know?
我  你开心了我也跟着高兴  兄弟
And, ah, I'm, uh, I'm just happy that you're happy, man.
兄弟  对不起
Oh, man, I, I'm so sorry,
-我应该  我应该陪着你的  -什么
- I should have, I should have been there for you. - What?
那次喝红酒画画
With the whole wine and paint thing.
看看你吧  你变了
Because look at you, you went ahead and you...
你长出阴道来了
...you grew a vagina.
你个傻逼
Oh, you fucker.
是的  对  但  我在想
Yeah, right, but like, I'm, I'm thinking
他简直就是个变态  什么毛病
he's a straight fucking perve, you know? Like, sick.
他就坐在那
Uh, uh, he's just sitting there
看着  然后勃起了吗
watching, getting a boner and shit?
都他们的是些什么
What the fuck is that?
但 但  他还挺好玩的  我同意
And, and, okay, look, he's funny as shit, I'll give you that.
不过  我有一个妹妹  你知道吗
But, like, I got a little sister, you know?
我不知道
I didn't know.
-不知道  -好吧  兄弟
- No. - Yeah, man,
所以我  我不能接受这个
so I, I, I can't get down with that.
知道吗
You know?
好吧  我觉得你得多读几遍
Yeah, I think you have to read it a couple of times.
是的  一开始是很形象  确实
Yeah, at first it's pretty graphic, yeah.
他妈的  我确实很有时间  对吧
Oh, fuck it, I got the time, right?
我隔几年读一次
I read it every couple of years.
每次感觉都不一样
Changes every time.
这部书还拍成了电影
There's a movie, too.
拍成电影了吗
They made a movie?
这玩意是怎么拍成电影的
How the hell did they ever make a movie out of this?
我不知道  兄弟  如果你是个父亲
I don't know, man. Look, like what if you were a dad?
你会狠揍他一顿  对吗
Now you'd beat the shit out of him, right?
听着  我不是最好的记者
Look, I am not the most accomplished journalist and shit,
但如果我
but if my…
嘿  惊喜吧
Hi, surprise.
-确实  -我饿了而且我想见你
- Yeah. - Well, I was hungry and I wanted to see you.
可以吗
That okay?
当然  当然可以
Yeah, yeah, of course.
看啊  辣妹亲了我  还给我带了晚餐
Oh, look a hot girl just kissed me and brought me dinner.
我还是站在外面
I better stand outside looking
像个傻子一样  笑着就好
like an idiot and smiling.
你想进来吗
Would you like to come in?
-当然  谢谢  -进来吧
- Yeah, thank you. - Oh, then please come in.
-厨房  -厨房在那边
- Kitchen? - Kitchen's that way.
再来点
More?
好
Yeah.
今天过得怎么样
So, how was your day?
挺好  挺好
It's good, it's fine.
就是一些
It's just sort of,
工作上的事  你呢
work stuff, hm. You?
-挺好  -都挺好的吗
-Yeah, mm-hm. -Everything good?
是吗
Yeah?
我只是在想我答应你的那个事
Well, I was just thinking about that promise I made you,
那个不
about not, um--
我
I...
有
...have an, oh,
看  我就知道在那
see? I just knew they were in there.
好多了
Better?
是的
Yeah.
是吗
Yeah?
好
Oh, yeah.
这样可以吗
Oh, hey, is this okay?
-当然  -我  我不想太着急
- Yeah. - Because I, I don't, I don't want to rush you.
没事了  好了  谢谢  谢谢
Okay, yeah, thank you, thank you.
-所以停了吗  -不  不
- So, stop? - No, no.
不  当然不能停
No? Absolutely not.
你还好吗
You okay?
-当然  -如你愿意  我们可以只抱抱
- Yeah. - Because we can just cuddle if you want to.
-不  当然不  -好  来吧
- No, absolutely not. - Sure, okay.
嘿  嘿  嘿  别  等等  等等
Hey, hey, hey, no, no, no! Wait, wait, hey, hey, hey.
等等  别别别
Wait, no, no, no, no!
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
离我远一点
Get the fuck away from me!
等等
Wait, wait,
等等  凯拉  凯拉  凯拉  等等
wait, Kyra, Kyra, Kyra. Wait,
等等  听我说
wait, please, just, just listen.
听着  我给你解释
Just listen, I'll explain.
听我解释  听我解释
I'll explain, I'll explain,
求你了  听我解释
I'll explain. Please, please.
我  我
I, I um…
我  他  他是  是他
I, he, he's, it's him.
就是他
He's the guy.
我  我抓住了他
I, I caught him.
那个男的  你刚刚看见的那个男的
The man, um, the man you just, you just saw?
他是  他是那个  他
He's, um, he's, he's the one, he--
他  他  他杀了我的妻子
he… he killed... he killed my wife.
我抓住了  好吧  我抓住了他
I tracked… I see, okay, I tracked him down...
-别  -然后他
- Don't. - ...and he.
我不知道该怎么做  好吗
I didn't know what to do, okay?
-我  我  我  -你  你干了什么
- I, I, I was, I was… - You did, you did what?
-你抓住他了  -我只是  我只是
- You tracked him down? - I just, I just,
好吧  我们能  你能回来我们谈谈吗
okay, can we, can you just come back in for like one second.
-你能回来吗  我们谈谈  -不
- Can you come back in, we'll talk. - No.
-就是那个人吗  -是的
- He's the guy? - Yeah.
-这他妈太操蛋了  克劳德  -我知道
- This is so fucked, Claude. - I know.
-是吗  -我知道  我知道  我知道
- Really? - I know, I know, I know.
我们能谈谈吗
Can we just talk?
谈谈  我才不会和你谈呢
Talk? I'm not having this conversation!
你在地下室折磨一个人
You're torturing a person in your basement!
-我  我知道  -你在干什么
- I… I know, I… - What are you doing?
怎么  你就这么关着他吗
What, are you just keeping him?
-我没有  凯拉  -什么
- I don't, Kyra… - What?
我他妈的应该远离你
I should have just stayed the fuck away from you.
好了  好了  好了  好了
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
你能  你能回来我们就谈一会
Can you just, um, can you just come back in for one second?
-回来  -我们就谈一会
- Come back? - And we'll talk for one second.
谈什么
Talk about what?
我会解释的  我会解释所有事情
I'll explain, I'll explain everything.
解释  已经很清楚
Explain? It's pretty clear.
混蛋  克劳德  我不能  我
Son of a bitch, Claude, I can't! I…
操  我必须
Fuck, I have to--
如果是你呢
What if it was you?
我不知道
I didn't know.
你让我应该怎么做  我
What would you have me do? I…
我不知道该做什么
I didn't know what to do!
我真的不知道
I didn't know, please.
我应该说什么呢  克劳德
What am I supposed to say to that, Claude?
什么
What?
难道我应该感到高兴吗
I'm supposed to be flattered?
不  不  我  我
No, no, I was, I--
你在你地下室里关着一个人
You have a man chained up in your fucking basement,
克劳德  于我这可不是从此就幸福快乐了
Claude, that's not exactly happily ever after for me.
凯拉
Kyra.
你  你对她说什么了
Did you... what did you say to her?
-我什么都没说  -你说了什么
- Look, I didn't say anything. - What did you say?
我发誓  我什么都没说
I swear to God, I didn't say anything to her!
-你对她说了么  -别  别  别
- What did you say her? - No, no, no, no!
杀了我
Do it.
杀了我  杀了我  杀了我
Do it, do it, do it, do it, do it.
杀啊  动手啊
Do it, do it, do it!
动手  动手啊
Do it, do it!
你个懦夫  你个怂货
You fucking coward! You fucking coward!
你他妈的
You fuck…
你把  你把她弄跑了
You took, took her from me.
你  你  你
You took, you took, you took...
让她离开了我
...took her from me.
你想谈谈吗
You want to talk about it?
你还好吗
You good?
什么
What?
很好
Yeah.
没什么  我很好
Whatever, yeah.
尝试感受画家的视线
Really try to channel the artist's vision.
我想我要从这桥上跳下去
I think I'm going to jump off the bridge.
理解他的目的
Capture his determination.
那应该很有趣
This was supposed to be fun.
他的那份热情
His passion.
他为什么选择画这个
Why did he choose this subject?
你为什么会在这  在这重新创造它
Why are you here, right now recreating it?
喝着红酒
Sipping wine.
-很有力  -我自己也这么认为
- Powerful. - I thought so myself.
你说完了吗  你说完了吗
Are you done? Are you done?
很好  那是个
Good. Uh, that is a
有趣的策略
very interesting strategy
鉴于此
and considering that
我又觉得的信心  你实在
I am absolutely confident that you are way too
蠢到让我无法帮忙
fucking stupid for me to help.
祝好
All the best.
走吧  他们等着呢
Let's go, they're waiting.
来吧
Come.
这太反常了
This is anti-climatic.
我知道  我知道  他从来不在
I know, I know, he's never there.
我们都在这站着
We're all standing around
-好像我们不知道  -好了
- like we don't know… - All right.
-他来了吗  -来了  他刚才打电话呢
- Is he coming? - Yeah, he was just on the phone.
-他来了  -好  都到齐了吗
- There he is. - All right, are we all here?
谢谢你  磨蹭蛋  好了
Thank you, slow poke, okay.
又度过了很棒的一年
Another big year folks!
你们都很棒
You guys were amazing!
说真的  这有点奇怪
Seriously, oh, oh, that's weird.
这有什么东西  抱歉
There's something, I'm sorry,
这有什么东西刮着我
there's something scratching.
我不知道这是啥
I don't know what that,
真奇怪  是张支票
oh, that's weird, it's a check.
是你放进去的吗
Did you put that in?
-不是我  -不是  好吧  真奇怪
- No. - No, okay, that's weird.
是15000美元
Oh, it's for $15,000.
欢呼吧
and cheering
这真是超棒  天呐
That is a nice… Oh, oh, my God.
-怎么了  -有什么东西  你看到了吗
- What? - Is there something? Do you see any?
有什么奇怪的东西卡在
I have this weird thing sticking out of my--
对  在这  卡在我的塑身衣上
Yeah, it's here. It's like caught on my Spanx.
对  是了  好了
Yeah, there's something. All right.
这个
Oh, this!
我记起来了  对  我记得我放在我的
I remember, okay, I remember I put this in my,
好了  两个费用全包的旅行名额  去
all right, two tickets for an all-expense paid trip to
-夏威夷  -夏威夷
- Hawaii! - Hawaii!
♪ 夏威夷  夏威夷 ♪
♪ Hawaii, Hawaii ♪
我的天
Oh, my goodness.
你们知道的  一个小礼物送给
So, you know, just a little something to congratulate
年度最佳销售员  好奇是谁呢
number one sales person of the year. Wonder who that could be?
不卖关子了  这个人今年过得很艰难
There's no suspense, look, this person has had a rough year.
是吧  我们  我们都看得到
Right, we, we can all acknowledge that. I mean,
他经历了一些
he's been through some things
我们甚至都无法想象的事
that we can't even imagine, and...
但重要的是  他克服各种困难撑下来了
...the thing is he, he persevered, you know?
他不仅每天来上班  还做得很出色
And he showed up every single day and he kicked some ass,
这值得大家为他鼓掌
and that's-- that deserves some applause.
这是个值得钦佩的人
This person is someone to be admired.
克劳德·沃恩  你人呢  他在哪
Claude Vaughn, where you at? Where is he?
快过来
Get over here! Yeah!
掌声响起来
Give it up
给我们的销售第一名
for our number one sales rep!
-快过来  -克劳德  克劳德
-Come on down.  - Claude, Claude,
克劳德  克劳德  克劳德  克劳德
Claude, Claude, Claude, Claude.
快来拿你的票
Come take the tickets.
你可以的
You got it. Woo, hoo!
现在你收获一份打屁屁奖励
Now you get your spanking!
我要打你喔
I'm going to spank you!
没有  我开玩笑  我开玩笑的
No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding,
那可是性骚扰了
that would be harassment.
好了
All right.
-戴上了  -戴好了
- Ah, there you go. - There it is.
-第一名  第一名  -太棒了 兄弟
- Number one, number one! - Yeah, buddy.
恭喜
Congratulations.
真棒
Great job.
谁能想到经历了这些
Who would have thought it'd take something like this
才让我戒了毒瘾
for me to get clean, huh?
我都不记得上次吸是什么时候了
I can't even remember the last time.
我那会需要钱  我想要
I needed money, I wanted--
我想要钱
I wanted money.
去买毒品
To score.
事情  事情开始变得很糟
It was-- It was getting pretty bad.
我们  我们本来打算拿了钱就出来
We were, we were supposed to be in and out.
然后我看到她站在那
And I saw her standing there
站在边上
off to the side.
她看上去并不害怕  或怎样
She didn't look scared, or nothing.
她看起来挺有钱的
She had nice stuff.
你知道的  很贵的包  很大的钻戒
You know, big bag, big rings.
所以我走了过去
So I walked over to her.
她真的很漂亮
She was real pretty.
我抢过她的包  然后说"把戒指给我"
I snatched her bag and I say, "Give me the fucking rings."
她不愿意
She wouldn't do it.
她没给  她
She wouldn't do it, she--
我就来火了
It just made me mad.
她把我惹毛了  所以我说
She made me real fucking mad, man, so I said,
"他妈的把戒指给我"
"Give me the fucking rings,"
我用枪指着她的脸
and I'm pointing my gun in her face.
我真的只是想吓吓她
I was just trying to scare her, man.
我发誓我他妈真的只是想吓吓她
I swear to God I was just trying to fucking scare her.
操
Fuck.
太操蛋了
Hey, well, fuck it, you know.
但这不是借口
There are no, there are no excuses.
你想怎么处置我都行
Do what you got to do, man.
我都理解
I get it.
随你处置
Do what you got to do.
我想休息一段时间
I'm just going to take some time.
或许把那两张票用了
Maybe use those tickets.
-没问题  -就是
-Good. - There's just a--
有些我一直拖着没做的事
a few things I've been pushing off for a little too long.
你说得没错
You're right, well,
知道吗  你的办公室会一直给你留着
you know what? That office is going to be waiting for you
无论什么时候你想回来
whenever you're ready.
甚至换一间更大的
And you know what, maybe even a bigger one.
我很感激
I appreciate that.
下次肯定不会在厕所旁边了
Next time not next to the shitter.
那最好了
That'd be nice.
-我们会再见的  -好的
-Okay. We'll see you. - Ah, okay.
-好了  -这感觉很好
- Okay. - Ah, yes, it's nice.
好了  可以了  谢谢
All right, thanks. Thank you.
我们会想你的
We're going to miss you. Oh.
我们还是能一起出去玩的  对吧
Okay. We're still going to chill, right?
当然  当然
Yeah, yeah, of course.
那就好
Okay. Okay.
好的兄弟  我们回头见
All right buddy, we'll see you.
抱我
Hold me.
不要吗
No?
车很干净  也好开  只是撞了一下
She's clean, she drives pretty well, she's a little banged up,
不过  你要不要试驾一下
but, uh, you want to take her for a test drive?
看看你今天买的
Hey, look at you!
真为你骄傲
I'm so proud.
谢谢
Thank you.
我要你仔细听我说
I need you to listen to me.
于我  你已经死在那个地下室了
As far as I know, you died in that basement.
谢谢你
Thank you for...
没有告诉任何人
...not calling anyone.
我当时不知道应该怎么
I didn't know how to...
告诉你
...tell you,
那个  我  我  我
that I-I-I had my...
杀了我妻子的凶手
wife's...
在我手上
...murderer.
如果如实告知  我很担心你对我的看法
You know, or what you'd think of me if I did.
我明白  很难的选择
Yeah, tough one.
我想过打电话
I thought about calling.
打给你  不是报警或什么别的
You, not the police or anything.
骗你的  其实我差点就报警了
That's not true, I almost called.
实在太难以接受了
It's hard to digest.
我尝试着去理解你
I mean I tried to understand it.
然后我觉得你是个疯子
And then I just think that you're an insane person.
是啊
Yeah.
我也曾经这么觉得
Been there.
然后呢
And?
他消失了
He's gone.
我  我  我放他走了
I-I-I let him go.
莱利夫妇来上了一次课
The Rileys came in for another lesson.
大吵了一架然后走了
Got in a fight and left.
他们买了
I mean, they bought
很多节课  所以
like a dozen lessons, so.
我觉得她可能
I think she might get--
我有两张去夏威夷的票
I got these tickets and stuff to Hawaii.
公司奖励我的
I won them at work.
一共7天  有按摩什么的  一整套
It's seven days, and massages, the whole works.
钓鱼  潜水
Fish, scuba.
我想着可以下周去
I'm thinking about going next week.
下周
Next week?
我还从来没去过夏威夷
I've never been to Hawaii.
我也是
Me neither.
-听起来很棒  -是啊
- Sounds nice. - Yeah.
你  你是在邀请我一起去夏威夷吗
Are you-- are you asking me to go to Hawaii with you?
是啊
Yeah.
好啊
Okay.
真的吗
Okay?
真的
Okay.
-配了一套  -绝对不要
-They match. - Absolutely not.
-干嘛  -不行  不行
- What? - No, no.
-那可是夏威夷  -别穿成那样
-It's Hawaii. - Don't be that guy.
怎么  那我是不是应该带上草裙
What, should I pack my grass skirt?
有道理
Point taken.
好吧  如果你真的有
Okay, you know, if you did have
椰壳胸衣
a coconut bra, though,
传统夏威夷女性服饰  用椰壳制成的内衣
我觉得我会感兴趣的
I think I'd be interested in that.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
行李箱位置不够了
Hm, no room.
要么椰壳内衣要么可食用内裤
It was that or the edible panties.
真会挑  我上飞机上就会饿
Good choice, because I get hungry on planes.
我很容易湿的
I get swamp ass.
那正好可以直接喝了
Yeah, we're going to beeline straight for the water, then.
可食用情趣内裤一般由糖做成  潮湿的情况下内裤可能会融化
-好的  -好
- Okay. - Yeah.
对了  你有没有那种
Oh, hey, do you have any of those, um...
带管子的面罩
...masky tubey things?
带管子的面罩  潜水呼吸面罩吗
Masky tubey things? Snorkels?
-呼吸面罩 对  -有  我记得我
- Snorkels, yes! - Yeah, I think I got, um--
-买新的吧  -那就买新的
- Get new ones? - Let's get new ones.
-嗯  -好  就这么办
- Mm-hm. - Yeah, okay, cool.
好  买新的
Yeah, new ones. Okay.
我们出发吧  好吗
Let's get out of here, ready?
-你准备好了吗  -准备好了
- You ready? - Yes.
好的
Okay.
早啊
Morning.
早上好
Good morning.
我
I, uh...
要去旅游吗
Going on a trip?
是啊
Yeah.
去夏威夷
Uh, Hawaii.
麦吉探长  这是  这是凯拉
Uh, Detective McGee, this is, this is Kyra.
凯拉这是麦吉警探
Uh, Kyra this is, um, Detective McGee.
他是负责案子的
He's handling, uh, uh, the case.
很高兴认识你
Hi, nice to meet you.
你有时间吗
You got a minute?
当然
Okay, sure, yeah.
请进
Please.
你最近怎么样
How you been?
挺好的
Fine.
没见你打给我
Never called.
我听从了你的建议
I've been taking your advice.
很好
Good.
你的手怎么样了
How's your hand?
好多了
Better.
这段时间没练了
Hm, taking a break.
打沙袋  对吧
Hitting the bag, right?
对
Right.
我能看看吗
Can I see it?
那个沙袋  当然可以
The bag, yeah. Yeah.
跟我来
Follow me.
没戴手套
No gloves.
我能喝杯水吗
Think I could get a glass of water?
好的
Yeah.
你们在一起多久了
How long you two been, uh?
-不久  -几个月吧
- Not long. - A few months.
那很好
That's good.
-探长  -我能问问你昨晚在哪吗
- Detective-- - Can I ask you where you were last night?
我们昨晚出去吃晚饭还看了电影
Yeah, we went out to dinner and then a film.
在哪儿
Where?
嗨雾餐厅  然后在公园看了《热身舞》
High Misty and they were playing "Dirty Dancing" at the park.
1987年上映的一部美国歌舞爱情片
还有别人跟你们一起吗
Anyone else with you?
有  我的朋友  莱利夫妇
Yeah, my friends, the Rileys.
米奇  你问这些是要干嘛
Mitch, what is this all about?
昨晚我们发现了洛根·柯比的尸体
Found Logan Kirby's body last night.
胸口中了两枪
Shot twice in the chest.
似乎我们并不是唯一在找他的人
Seems like we weren't the only ones looking for him.
不过  奇怪的是  看起来他被
Weird thing was, though, it seemed like he was,
怎么说  虐待过
I don't know, tortured.
你知道这事儿吗
You know anything about that?
不知道吗
No?
那你呢
How about you?
不知道
No.
那好吧  事情就是这样了
Well, all that is what it is now.
我的意思是  他们这种人
I mean, these types get themselves
总是会卷进各种各样的麻烦
into all sorts of trouble.
但是杀人  那就性质完全不一样了
But murder, that's a different game.
上帝明白我能理解  但我还是得问
Lord knows I'd understand, but I got to ask.
是你杀了洛根·柯比吗
Did you murder Logan Kirby?
我之前想的
I wanted to.
但我下不了手
But I couldn't do it.
祝你们假期愉快
Have a good vacation.
你还好吗
You okay?